[I found you, WOONHAK!]
I found you!
I'm going, okay
Please, I'm sorry
Don't scare me like that
[WOONHAK's scream]
Oh my goodness
Go away! I'm sorry
I'm sorry, you got me
You got me, I'm sorry
Okay
I get it, I'm serious
I lost my voice
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
[Phone vibration]
[Phone notification]
Once you it 2,222 seconds of playtime,
the seeker will leave
to give you four minutes
to hide yourselves better
More than half the time is gone
After the four minutes pass,
two seekers will come for you, so hide
That means
there's just one seeker right now
[Seeker's footstep]
[SUNGHO]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN haven't checked the text yet]
- Should we take the elevator?
- Get on
I can't save anyone anymore, I'm tired
Third floor
Let's just go back and forth
on the elevator
We can head down if the seeker comes
[The seeker disappears]
[Four minutes of free time for BOYNEXTDOOR]
Where's the seeker?
Can you see them right now?
First floor
Should we head up or no?
Let's head up
[These two don't know the seeker is gone yet]
Four minutes?
I have four minutes
[RIWOO]
Should we head out?
[RIWOO heads out after a while]
[Meanwhile, JAEHYUN and LEEHAN
head back to the first floor]
Do we get off or not?
What do you want to do?
Do we get off here? What do we do?
First floor
- Let's just make a run for it
- Okay
The seeker went up here
You don't need to hide for four minutes
- Huh?
- Check your text, there's no seeker
for four minutes
- Really?
- Then let's go to the third floor
What?
We were so nervous for no reason
We don't need to hide for four minutes?
- How come I didn't check that?
- I didn't know either
Third floor, the doors are opening
[JAEHYUN and LEEHAN get off on the third floor]
[RIWOO looks for keys]
Do you know where the key is?
- Have you found one yet?
- I found one
- What about you?
- I haven't found one
But the hint was a photo
of this merry-go-round
[Key hint]
I feel like it's this way
Huh? Is this the key?
[Got the fourth key on the merry-go-round]
Huh? Yeah, it is
- Should I take it?
- Yeah
We found the one here,
we better hide now
[RIWOO and TAESAN hide after getting the key]
[SUNGHO]
But
I hid at a pretty obvious spot
How come they can't find me?
[SUNGHO doesn't know it's free time right now]
I took a photo
and they said I can leave with this
A scared...
[Phone notification]
A different member took the key
at the photo booth
Oh, I don't get a key
for taking a photo
[WOONHAK's sigh]
Ready or not
Here I come
Let's hide back at the spot
we were in before
As long as I have a key, it's fine
This is the best spot
Ready or not
here I come
[TAESAN]
Ready or not
Now you have to deal with two seekers
[JAEHYUN and LEEHAN made a spot to hide in together]
now you have to deal with two seekers
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
Ready or not
[SUNGHO heads out right as the seekers come back]
Are you all hiding?
I'm coming to get you
[The seeker is on the first floor]
[Starts searching for the members]
[The other seeker is on the second floor]
[Second floor] [Seeker] [Seeker] [SUNGHO]
[SUNGHO heads out late]
[Analyzing what's happening
by listening to the seeker's footsteps]
I thought we got four minutes of free time
[Mistook the ending song
as the start of free time]
[SUNGHO↓] [←Seeker]
Wait, I thought we got four minutes
[SUNGHO heads back, sensing something is off]
[The seeker gets closer to SUNGHO]
[SUNGHO] [Seeker]
I found you, SUNGHO!
Oh my goodness...
I thought we got four minutes of free time
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
Oh my goodness...
Hi
I think...
- I think I misunderstood the rules
- Why?
I thought once the music played
- we got four minutes to hide again
- Yeah
I thought the song was going to play
throughout the four minutes
You're a dummy too
Is my reading comprehension just weird?
[The seeker seeks high and low for the members]
[Phone vibration]
Two members are in jail
They get caught really easily
[Seeker's footsteps]
[TAESAN] [Seeker]
Two members are in jail
Wait
Do I have to go save WOONHAK?
[TAESAN has the key RIWOO found]
[Seeker's footsteps]
[Noise from the seeker]
[TAESAN]
It's back
[The seeker misses TAESAN and just walks away]
It left
I'm sweating
[TAESAN]
[The seeker walks away from TAESAN]
It's coming
Be quiet!
[The seeker gets closer to RIWOO]
[RIWOO]
[Heads where RIWOO is hiding]
[Seeker] [RIWOO]
[Sound of the seeker searching]
[Seeker]
[Misses RIWOO and walks away]
It was just here
but I guess it missed me
because of the lighting
Thank goodness I survived
[Third floor] [JAEHYUN, LEEHAN] [Seeker]
[The other seeker is on the third floor]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
It's here
- I should've closed that
- Yeah, should I go close it?
Just so we can hear if they're here
If we stay under the sheet,
there's no way the seeker will come
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[JAEHYUN CAM]
[Seeker's footsteps]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[JAEHYUN CAM]
- Did the seeker go down?
-I think so
I'm sweating so much right now
It's so hot
I'm with JAEHYUN right now
[The seeker moves from the first floor
to the second floor]
[TAESAN]
Okay, I better go save a member
What?
Who do I save?
Me
I have six minutes left
Oh, okay
- That's how the key looks like?
- Can you free WOONHAK?
Where did you find that?
- In the cabinet?
- No, the merry-go-round
- Then go to the white, yellow cabinet
- I know where that is
- It's on the second floor
- I'll go
[Seeker] [WOONHAK]
The seeker is right in front of us
The seeker is on the left
Let's go
[↑Seeker] [WOONHAK→]
[The seeker heads back to the stage]
[WOONHAK] [TAESAN]
[Seeker]
[WOONHAK quietly heads to the second floor]
[Safely makes it to the locker room]
[Meanwhile, TAESAN lingers in front of the prison]
Where do I go?
[Seeker's footsteps]
[Seeker] [TAESAN]
I'll try to hide again
[RIWOO]
[Couldn't find him and turns back again]
[Seeker] [TAESAN]
[Seeker's footsteps]
[TAESAN↓] [←Seeker]
[TAESAN]
I think they saw me
I found you, TAESAN!
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
I got caught again
[Phone notification]
What is it?
[Two members are in jail]
-  Someone got caught?
- Yeah, two members got caught
The seeker is here
[Seeker]
[Phone ringing]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
Turn your phone off
[The seeker follows the sound of the ringing]
[JAEHYUN, LEEHAN]
[Seeker]
[I found you, JAEHYUN and LEEHAN]
I found you!
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
I got a text
The key hint is a big cabinet on 2F
and a sled on 3F
There's no point in getting the keys
if you're going to get caught again
This is the way to go
I'll try my best to survive
[Phone ringing]
WOONHAK, I got caught
I'll come save you,
just wait for a bit
I promise to go save you
No, where is it?
[Can't find the locker with the key]
[WOONHAK]
[WOONHAK spends a while looking through the lockers]
[Key hint]
[Checks the locker number late]
[Starts his hunt for locker number 170]
Wait, there's no number 170
It's not here
If it's not here, then where is it?
[Finally found locker number 170]
[Found the key]
How do I take it out?
[WOONHAK]
What do I do?
How do I take it out?
How do I remove this?
[Seeker's footsteps]
[Second floor]
[Seeker] [WOONHAK]
[The seeker heads back down]
ONEDOOR! I'll find another way
to give you guys a gift
Yeah, ONEDOOR! We...
- We'll gift you guys in another way
- I'm sorry
We have no skills with this game
I had no idea
we would do this poorly
Yeah
Hey, WOONHAK!
Hurry and save someone,
we'll win if you do
[Two keys left, survival rate of 33.3%]
We just need to save one more person
[WOONHAK heads to locker number 170 again]
[Found the fifth key in the big locker]
[Heads straight to prison]
Who do I save?
- Save anyone
- Save him, he knows where the key is
WOONHAK, what floor were you on?
Where did you find the key?
- The place with the lockers
- Then let's go to the third floor
[Key hint]
[Sled - Third floor]
Let's all go to the third floor
You can save SUNGHO
No, you two can just go hide
No, you don't know so
save SUNGHO with a key
[One key left, survival rate of 50%]
You can do that too
[Phone notification]
We just have to hide
at the five-minute mark
What does the text say?
There are 444 seconds left...
[Phone notification]
[444 seconds left]
At the 444-second mark, shadows, that are faster than
the seekers will come into play
The moment the shadows find you,
they'll create a ruckus, don't get caught
Shadows are coming after us too
444 seconds...
Let's do our best, let's go!
[The shadows appear at the 444-second mark]
[TAESAN and WOONHAK halt their steps]
[Sound of the shadows]
[TAESAN, WOONHAK]
[Shadows]
[TAESAN and WOONHAK crouch down]
[Moves the moment the shadows pass by]
[TAESAN] [WOONHAK]
[Shadows]
We have to go to the third floor
[The shadows search for the members]
[The elevator arrives on the first floor]
Heading up
The front doors are closing
We have to find the sled
on the third floor
Then even if we get caught by a seeker
- we can use a key
- Yeah
[20 minute warning alarm]
What's this?
- I hit 20 minutes
- Is it over?
[20 minutes pass, SUNGHO can't leave now]
[JAEHYUN] [SUNGHO] [RIWOO]
[TAESAN] [LEEHAN] [WOONHAK]
[RIWOO]
[Lights off]
What's going on?
What is it?
[First floor]
[RIWOO] [Shadows]
The shadows
are right in front of me
[RIWOO]
[The shadows gather near RIWOO]
[But heads back, unable to find him]
Okay
[The elevator stops on the third floor]
Third floor
Hey, it's over here
[Key hint]
[The sled from the hint]
I found it!
[Got the final key from the sled]
WOONHAK, you have to hide now!
[The two hide in different spots]
[TAESAN heads to the storage room
and blocks the entrance]
Okay, we're good
[Third floor]
[TAESAN] [WOONHAK]
[WOONHAK heads to the corner of the third floor]
[WOONHAK's heavy breathing]
Huh? What's going on?
Don't we have less than a minute left?
There are 94 seconds left
Hey, we have 90 seconds left!
A minute and a half!
Don't get caught, please!
[Not even 100 seconds left]
[RIWOO, TAESAN, WOONHAK are the only three alive]
[WOONHAK heads towards the third floor stairs]
[Sound of the shadows]
[Turns back after hearing the shadows]
[The shadows head toward second floor]
[WOONHAK]
[Just as WOONHAK hides again]
[The seeker arrives on the third floor]
[←Seeker] [↑WOONHAK]
[Seeker's footsteps]
Someone is here
[WOONHAK] [TAESAN]
[The seeker heads toward TAESAN]
[TAESAN]
[I found you, TAESAN!]
Oh no
Oh no...
[WOONHAK]
WOONHAK, the seeker is over here!
[Another seeker arrives on the third floor]
Who are you?
[WOONHAK uses the chaos to run away]
[WOONHAK]
[Seeker] [WOONHAK]
WOONHAK, you have to survive!
[BOYNEXTDOOR's fate relies on WOONHAK]
[What's the outcome of the game?
- Oh no... one of us got caught...
- Oh no...
That was so close
- We only have 37 seconds left
- That's so close
I have to go to prison, right now!
I can just use the key
Heading down
How much time is left?
Let's hurry up
[WOONHAK ran away from the seeker]
- Oh...
That was so close
I have a key!
I'll free myself!
[Hide and seek is over]
You win this time
[Phone notification]
[Hide and seek is over, make your way to prison
to check BOYNEXTDOOR's survival rate]
I hid well
[Everyone gathered up at the prison]
Didn't we win?
- Wait, why is TAESAN here?
- Isn't it over?
- We lost
More than half got caught
If TAESAN escaped, we would've won
[Just then]
Wait, are you opening the door?
[The gatekeeper opens the door with TAESAN's key]
What's going on?
They just said
they'll accept the final escape
[With travel time to jail in mind,
TAESAN gets to escape]
Wow!
Good job, guys
[With a survival rate of over 50%,]
Success!
[ONEDOOR will get gifted snacks]
In the end, we made it
Good job
We made it
[The seeker's scream]
Did you think the game was over?